http://www.casewizard.com/privacy-policy

Start Your Free Trial
PRIVACY POLICYSafeguarding your privacy and the security of your personal information is important to us. Please take a few minutes to read the following policy so that you understand how we treat your personal information. As we continuously improve and expand our services, this policy might change, so please check it periodically. If you have questions about our privacy policy, please use the form on our Contact Us page.CaseWizard.com ("CASEWIZARD", "we," "our," "us") respects your privacy and values your trust and confidence. This privacy policy applies to the CASEWIZARD online and mobile web sites (www.casewizard.com, casewizard.com, casewizard.io, and *.casewizard.com) and the CASEWIZARD mobile applications owned and operated by CASEWIZARD. This privacy policy describes how CASEWIZARD collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web sites: www.casewizard.com, casewizard.com, casewizard.io, *.casewizard.com, and the mobile applications. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.PurposeCASEWIZARD has adopted this Privacy Policy in order to inform you of its policies with respect to information collected from the online and mobile web site (collectively, the "Web Sites") and our tablet and smartphone applications (the "Application" or collectively the "Applications"). Your use of the Web Sites or Applications constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your consent to the practices it describes.Personally Identifiable InformationPersonally Identifiable Information is any information that concerns you individually and would permit someone to contact you, for example, your name, address, telephone/fax number, email address or any information you submit to the Web Sites or the Applications that identifies you individually.The Web Sites or the Applications will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you provide it.You can visit and browse the Web Sites and the Applications without revealing personally identifiable information about yourself, but not all functions will be available to you. You may also choose to disclose personally identifiable information about yourself, which may be maintained as described below. The Web Sites and the Applications may collect personally identifiable information about you by methods such as the following:Registration Forms - If you are offered the opportunity to enter a promotion, to become a registered user of the Web Sites or Applications, or to opt-in to receive CASEWIZARD information through another site or the Applications, you must apply by filling out the registration form on the site or the Application. This form requires certain personally identifiable information that may include, without limitation, your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, areas of interest, product usage, credit/debit card number(s) with associated expiration date(s), CVV and billing zip code(s), and/or a unique individual password.Transactions and Activity - If you become a registered user or if you conduct transactions through the Web Sites or an Application, we will collect information about the transactions you engage in while on the Web Sites or Applications and your other activity on the Web Sites or Applications. This information may include, without limitation, areas of the Web Sites or Applications that you visit, transaction type, content that you view, geo location, download or submit, transaction amount, payment, and billing information as well as the nature, quantity and price of the goods or services you exchange and the individuals or entities with whom you communicate or transact business.Email and other voluntary communications - You may also choose to communicate with us through email, via our Web Sites, via the Applications, by telephone, in writing, or through other means. We collect the information in these communications, and such information may be personally identifiable.Non-Personally Identifiable InformationWhen you visit the CASEWIZARD Web Sites and Applications, like when you visit most other web sites and applications, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically logged, which may include information about the type of browser you use, the server name and IP address through which you access the internet (which identifies the company providing you internet access and general geographic information), the date and time you access the site, the pages you access while at the CASEWIZARD Web Sites or Applications, and the internet address of the web sites, if any, from which you linked directly to the CASEWIZARD Web Site or Application. Some of this information is personally identifiable.Information UseCASEWIZARD may use the personally identifiable information collected through its Web Sites or Applications primarily for such purposes as:helping to establish and verify the identity of users;opening, maintaining, administering and servicing users' accounts or memberships;processing, servicing or enforcing transactions and sending related communications;providing services and support to users;improving the Web Sites and Applications, including tailoring it to users' preferences;providing users with product or service updates, promotional notices and offers, and other information about CASEWIZARD and its affiliates;responding to your questions inquiries, comments and instructions;protecting our systems from fraud and unlawful access;maintaining the security and integrity of its systems;sending you a newsletter; andsending you marketing communications.CASEWIZARD uses the browsing information collected automatically by its servers primarily to help it administer and improve its Web Sites and Applications. CASEWIZARD may also use aggregated anonymous information to provide information about its Web Sites and Applications to potential business partners and other unaffiliated entities. This information is not personally identifiable.Disclosure of InformationCASEWIZARD does not provide personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties for their use in marketing directly to you. CASEWIZARD may use unaffiliated companies to help it maintain and operate its Web Sites, Applications, payment processing, or for other reasons related to the operation of its business, and those companies may receive your personally identifiable information for that purpose. These companies may only use such personally identifiable information for the purpose or performing those functions and may not use it for any other purpose. CASEWIZARD may also disclose personally identifiable information about you in connection with legal requirements, such as in response to an authorized subpoena, governmental request or investigation, or as otherwise permitted by law. If CASEWIZARD is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you may be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information."Cookies" and AdvertisersThe CASEWIZARD Web Sites' and Applications' servers, or the servers of companies that are used to operate the Web Sites and Applications, may place a "cookie" on your computer or store data in your computer browser in order to allow you to use the Web Sites and Applications and to personalize your experience. A "cookie" is a small piece of data that can be sent by a web server to your computer, which then may be stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies and browser storage allow us to recognize your computer while you are on our Web Sites and Applications and help customize your online experience and make it more convenient for you. Cookies and browser storage are also useful in allowing more efficient log-in for users, tracking transaction histories and preserving information between sessions. The information collected from cookies and browser storage may also be used to improve the functionality of the Web Sites and Applications.Most web browser applications (such as Microsoft Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Firefox and Apple Safari) have features that can notify you when you receive a cookie or prevent cookies from being sent. If you disable cookies, however, you may not be able to use certain  functions of the Web Sites or the Applications.Retargeting and Online Behavioral AdvertisingRetargeting is a way to use non-personal information to remind you on other websites that you were browsing CASEWIZARD Web Sites previously with the goal to bring you back to our site. CASEWIZARD may use the non-personal information collected on its Web Site for online behavioral advertising purposes including retargeting and to customize ads to you when you visit other (non-CASEWIZARD) sites.These companies typically use cookies, pixel tags/web beacons, and similar technologies to analyze your usage of our Web Sites. These third parties collect, and share with us, as we may request, non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you, including such web site usage information about visits to our Web Sites, measure and research the effectiveness of our advertisements, track page usage and paths followed during visits through our sites, help us serve relevant Internet banner advertisements on our sites and on other sites, and track use of our Internet banner advertisements and other links from our marketing partners' sites to our sites.Types of cookies and tags on our sites:Functionality: Used to remember your preferences for using the sites and for facilitating transactions such as purchases.Performance or Analytics: Used to anonymously measure site activity to improve visitor experience.Targeting: Used to display information and offers that specifically interest you.How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals (California Online Privacy Protection Act)Other than for the purposes expressly described above, CASEWIZARD does not track users across the web, and therefore does not use or respond to "do not track" signals. CASEWIZARD also does not authorize the collection of personally identifiable information from Website or App users for third party use through advertising technologies.Local Storage - HTML5We use Local Storage, such as HTML5 storage, to store information related to whether the user has chosen to "Remain Logged In" as well as tokens if third party services are used. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use Local Storage such as HTML5 storage to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 Local Storage.External LinksThe CASEWIZARD Web Sites and Applications may contain links to other web sites not maintained or related to CASEWIZARD. These links are provided as a service to users and are not sponsored by or affiliated with the Web Sites, Applications, or CASEWIZARD. CASEWIZARD has not reviewed any or all of the sites hyper-linked to or from the Web Sites or Applications and is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other web sites. The links are accessed at the user's own risk, and CASEWIZARD makes no representations or warranties about the content, completeness or accuracy of these links or the sites hyper-linked to the Web Sites or Applications. Web sites that are accessible by hyperlinks from the CASEWIZARD Web Sites or Applications may use cookies. CASEWIZARD encourages you to read the privacy statements provided by other web sites before you provide personally identifiable information to them. CASEWIZARD does not implicitly endorse third-party sites hyper-linked to the Web Sites or Applications.Social Media WidgetsOur Web Site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Pinterest button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.SecurityCASEWIZARD maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help guard personally identifiable information. If transactions are offered on the Web Sites or Applications, transaction information is transmitted to and from CASEWIZARD in encrypted form using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connections to help protect such information from interception. CASEWIZARD restricts authorized access to your personal information to those persons who have a legitimate purpose to know that information to provide products or services to you and those persons you have authorized to have access to such information. Credit/debit card number(s) you elect to provide on file as part of your online profile for use when placing an order through the CASEWIZARD Web Sites or Applications will be tokenized and maintained in an encrypted format by a third party provider to further lower any risk. It is your responsibility to protect the integrity of your own account by keeping your account name and password safe. Please be aware, however, that any email or other transmission you send through the internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception.Choice/Opt-OutIn order to provide service to you, we may send you communications related to your transactions, security or the administration of the Web Sites or Applications. From time to time, CASEWIZARD and its affiliates may also wish to send you other messages or updates about our Web Sites, Applications, CASEWIZARD, our affiliates, or their promotions and other activities. If you do not wish to receive non-transaction/security related communications from CASEWIZARD and its affiliates, please send an email containing your request via our Contact Us page.If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire to maintain an account, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, ask to have it removed from our site and system or deactivate it by making the change on your account or by emailing our Customer Support via our Contact Us page or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request for access within 30 days.We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.Changes to this Privacy PolicyCASEWIZARD reserves the right to modify or supplement this policy at any time. If a material change to the terms of this policy is made, CASEWIZARD will post a notice prior to the change becoming effective on its homepage and a link to the new policy.Contacting UsIf you have questions about this privacy statement, the information practices of CASEWIZARD or your dealings with our Web Sites or Applications, please use the link on our Contact Us page.CaseWizard.com, Inc.1201 Peachtree Street, 400 Colony SquareSuite 200Atlanta, GA 30361877-926-8367 Revision DateThis policy was last updated 01 May 2017.
